rouxbe.com 2007-10-30

# Rouxbe - The Recipe to Better Cooking

#### Privacy Policy

As of October 2006

**Children and parents click here!**

We care about your privacy and we are committed to ensuring that your privacy is respected and protected.

This privacy policy (this " _Policy_ ";) applies to [www.rouxbe.com](http://www.rouxbe.com/) (the " _Site_ ";), which is owned and operated by Rouxbe Video Technologies Inc., its parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates (collectively, " _Rouxbe_ ";). Except as provided below, we do not collect any personally identifiable information about you while you use the Site. Please read this Policy very carefully. In addition to reviewing this privacy policy, please read our Terms of Use Agreement. Your use of the Site constitutes agreement to applicable laws and the terms and conditions contained on the Site, in this Policy, and in the Terms of Use Agreement. This Policy does not cover information collected on sites linked to from this Site.

Rouxbe reserves the right to change this Policy at any time without notice and by using this Site subsequent to any revision of the Policy; you agree to be bound by such changes. We will post any changes to this Policy on this Site. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy and familiarize yourself with the most current version. We will use any information collected in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is collected.

#### The Type of Information we Collect

Any personally identifiable information you provide is voluntary. The cases in which we do collect personally identifiable information are as follows:

#### Registration

In order to access and use certain services provided through the Site, you must complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as a name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

You may also have the option to provide demographic information (such as income level, age and gender) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so that we can provide you a more personalized experience on our Site.

#### Subscription

When you subscribe to our service through our Site (the " _Service_ ";), we require that you provide certain personally identifiable information, including your name, address, phone number, credit card number, or account number. This information is necessary to process your subscription and to contact you.

#### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our Site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal code).

We use this information to notify contest winners, award prizes, monitor Site traffic, personalize Site, contact you, and to evaluate Site access demographics. We may also announce names of contest winners on the Site.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

#### Requesting an invite

We allow you the opportunity to request to have one of our partners pay for your access to our Service. In order to get this paid access, you may be asked to complete a survey, which may contain certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys is voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), demographic information (such as postal code) and information about your culinary interests.

We use this information to align you with the most appropriate partner who may best serve your interests. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

#### Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Rouxbe stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [privacy@rouxbe.com](mailto:privacy@rouxbe.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

#### How we use the Information we collect

We use information you supply through the Site to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to any of our Service, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice. Similarly, if you enter an online competition, we will use this information to notify you if you are a winner. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, or to improve the Service that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.

Rouxbe does not sell our users' e-mail addresses. However, unless otherwise specified, we may share e-mail addresses and sell or share all other information with our affiliates and with carefully selected companies who we think can offer you services and products of interest to you. If you do not wish to have your information shared, write to us at privacy@rouxbe.com. If you do not wish to receive future commercial communications from us by e-mail, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail. If you've registered on any part of the Site, we will provide an online method to change or update your member preferences or information on the Site, or you can send us an e-mail with your revised preferences or information to [privacy@rouxbe.com](mailto:privacy@rouxbe.com).

#### Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page.

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the Opt-out Section below.

#### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the Opt-out Section.

#### Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

#### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

#### Profile

We may store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and/or third party sources to create a "profile"; of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you.

#### Supplementation of Information

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

#### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users.

#### Service Providers

We use other third parties to provide us with services, such as, credit card processing, technical maintenance, or online recruitment services for the purpose of providing such services on our site. When you sign up for subscription services we will share your information with such services providers for credit card processing and order fulfillment, as necessary.

We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While we will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

#### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site.

#### Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [privacy@rouxbe.com](mailto:privacy@rouxbe.com), or you may contact us at:

Privacy Policy Coordinator:   
Rouxbe.com  
269 East 45th Avenue  
Vancouver, BC  
Canada V5W 1X2  
(604) 677-6000

#### Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help"; file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you do not have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Site. We use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns, to deliver content, and to record registration.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this Site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### Links to Other Sites

This Site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Rouxbe. Please be aware that we, Rouxbe, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Site.

#### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [privacy@rouxbe.com](mailto:privacy@rouxbe.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

#### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and) on our registration or order forms, we ensure that information is encrypted using our own encryption tolls or through our third party payment processor. Encryption is done using secure socket layer technology ("SSL";).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Site, you can send email us at privacy@rouxbe.com.

#### Business Transitions

In the event Rouxbe goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

#### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Privacy Policy Coordinator  
Rouxbe.com  
269 East 45th Avenue   
Vancouver, BC   
Canada V5W 1X2

#### CHILDREN AND PARENTS

This Site is not intended for use by anyone under 18 years old. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums, and chats.

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of this Site, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.

If you are worried about your children's activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator at [privacy@rouxbe.com](mailto:privacy@rouxbe.com).

If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator at privacy@rouxbe.com. We welcome your feedback. You can also send us regular mail at the following address:

Privacy Policy Coordinator  
Rouxbe.com  
269 East 45th Avenue   
Vancouver, BC   
Canada V5W 1X2
